<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Westley Winks</title>
    <link>https://westleywinks.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Westley Winks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://westleywinks.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://westleywinks.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://westleywinks.com/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://westleywinks.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://westleywinks.com/books/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khalti in the Taxi</title>
      <link>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/khalti-in-the-taxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/khalti-in-the-taxi/</guid>
      <description>I had just said goodbye to my first host family, to the Peace Corps staff, and to the volunteers that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t see for the next three months. I was now on my way to my final site to live there for the next two years.
I had all of my belongings; those that I brought from home and the couple of things I had acquired here. I was to take a total of three taxis that day, the first of which was shared with some other volunteers and &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo; luggage (In reality, it was one volunteer&amp;rsquo;s luggage that took up most of the space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settling In and Housekeeping</title>
      <link>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/settling-in-and-housekeeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/settling-in-and-housekeeping/</guid>
      <description>Housekeeping Finally. Four months in and things have calmed down enough where I have time to write about this wonderful culture and experience that I find myself in.
In this initial post, I will talk more specifically about my role here, what my life has looked liked during training, where I am now, and how I got here. After that, this blog/newsletter will be used mainly to share stories that highlight aspects of Moroccan culture as I experience it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Assignment</title>
      <link>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/2022-08-22_the-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://westleywinks.com/peace-corps/2022-08-22_the-assignment/</guid>
      <description>On December 24, 2020, I applied for the Peace Corps. I was entering my last terms of college and knew that I wanted to join the Peace Corps when I graduated.
A year and a half and one pandemic later, I received an official invite: Youth Development Specialist in Morocco set to depart September 2022. After reading the invite and job description, I did a fist pump, had a small joyful cry on the porch, and accepted the position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
